{
  "message": "Successfully uploaded",
  "questions": [
    {
      "explanation": "Answer: down",
      "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.",
      "comprehension":
        "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ",
      "question_type": 2,
      "answer": 1,
      "options": ["mouse", "down", "and", "when"]
    },
    {
      "explanation": "Answer: awakened",
      "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).",
      "comprehension":
        "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ",
      "question_type": 2,
      "answer": 0,
      "options": ["awakened", "soon", "to", "on"]
    },
    {
      "explanation": "Answer: lion",
      "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.",
      "comprehension":
        "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ",
      "question_type": 2,
      "answer": 3,
      "options": ["big", "huge", "soon", "lion"]
    },
    {
      "explanation": "Answer: his",
      "question": "In the following sentence identify Possessive pronoun.",
      "comprehension":
        "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ",
      "question_type": 2,
      "answer": 1,
      "options": ["mouse", "his", "to", "and"]
    },
    {
      "explanation": "Answer: began",
      "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).",
      "comprehension":
        "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ",
      "question_type": 2,
      "answer": 2,
      "options": ["when", "running", "began", "little"]
    },
    {
      "explanation": "Answer: jaws",
      "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.",
      "comprehension":
        "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ",
      "question_type": 2,
      "answer": 0,
      "options": ["jaws", "paw", "and", "huge"]
    },
    {
      "explanation": "Answer: him",
      "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.",
      "comprehension":
        "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ",
      "question_type": 2,
      "answer": 2,
      "options": ["king", "began", "him", "of"]
    },
    {
      "explanation": "Answer: king",
      "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.",
      "comprehension":
        "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ",
      "question_type": 2,
      "answer": 0,
      "options": ["king", "and", "the", "Once"]
    },
    {
      "explanation": "Answer: big",
      "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.",
      "comprehension":
        "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ",
      "question_type": 2,
      "answer": 2,
      "options": ["the", "soon", "big", "his"]
    },
    {
      "explanation": "Answer: running",
      "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (present participle).",
      "comprehension":
        "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ",
      "question_type": 2,
      "answer": 0,
      "options": ["running", "when", "and", "lion"]
    }
  ],
  "success": 1
}
